ZoLi Privacy Statement
======================

This document was last updated on September 18, 2019

1. **Acknowledgement and acceptance of terms**

ZoLi, Inc. ("ZoLi") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing the URL www.zoli-inc.com or any other site owned by ZoLi (the "Site"), you acknowledge that you understand and agree to this Privacy Statement ("Statement"), and consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Statement. You further acknowledge and agree that you are at least 18 years old. If you are under 18 years old, you do not have permission to access this site. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

2. **Participating Third Party Policies**

The Site may contain links to related services and offerings, including vendor sites. These third parties may have their own privacy statements that can be viewed on their websites or by contacting these third parties directly. These third parties who participate in ZoLi's services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since ZoLi does not have direct control over the policies or practices of third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of these third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

3. **Information We Collect and How We Use It**

ZoLi collects certain information from and about our users three ways: (1) directly from its web server logs, (2) with cookies, and (3) from you, the user. We do not collect information about the specifics of who you are ("Personally Identifiable Information") unless you specifically provide it to us.

4. **Web Server Logs**

When you visit our Site, we may track information to administer the Site and analyze its usage. None of this information is Personally Identifiable Information.

The personally identifiable information that you provide to us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. We also use Pixel Tags to collect additional information regarding your browsing experience. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient and to provide you with a more relevant and timely brand and shopping experience. This information may also be shared with our third party service providers that assist us with our marketing efforts and with other marketers whose products or services we feel may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other marketers, please email us at customerservice@zoli-inc.com
